hi and welcome to Tutorial
I'm leveling it
We have lots to cover in this course what kinds
of things we're gonna look at
Well we're going to review the The core components and
take a look at new aspects of working with Hadoop
such as a data lake
We're going to set up a dupe development environment that's
going to include the use of modern library's such a
spark
Speaking of spark we're going to go pretty deep looking
at how spark runs and we're gonna look at spark
libraries
Such a CZ sparks equal spark our and spark ML
Now in addition to Spark we're going to discuss some
of the other libraries that are commonly found in Hadoop
pipelines
Apache Kafka and other Cloud Service is for streaming in
jest
We're gonna pull it all together and look at use
cases and modern Hadoop pipelines and architectures
We have a lot to learn so let's get started